

# ABOUT

Hi, Welcome to my CV. My name is Juel Hossain. I am 23 years old. I am from, Dhaka, Bangladesh. I am a husband ,A Javascript Programmer, designer, web developer and An Automation Engineer. I am Open To Work and Willing to Relocate.

# **EDUCATIONS**

# **Primary School**

Panpara Govt. Primary School 2005 - 2009

5 Years To complete. Grade was first class.

## **Junior School**

Babupur Kasimuddin Bidyapith 2010 - 2012

3 Years To Complete. Grade was Gpa 3.21.

## **Electric Engineering.**

Rajbari Govt. Technical School and college

4 Years to Complete, dropped After six months.

# Secondary School

Hammadia High School

2014-2016

2.3 years to complete. Subject Was Business Study. Grade was Gpa 4.61.

# **Higher Secondary School**

Government Bangla College 2016-2018

2 years to complete, 1st year completed. Subject was Business. Dropped from 2nd year.

# CONTACT

+8801567954398

Juelhossainnn@gmail.com

https://juel-hossain.com

https://github.com/juelhossain

in https://linkedin.com/in/juelhossainnn

# **JUEL HOSSAIN**

JAVACRIPT PROGRAMMER

## **EXPERIENCES**

## **Small Business**

CYBER CAFE SHOP OWNER 2018 - 2019

After dropped out from the college. I have started This business.

# **Ride Sharing**

UBER AND PATHAO LTD.

2019 - 2020

Business didn't go well so I started Ride Sharing with Uber and instant Percel delivery with Pathao Ltd. At the same time.

## Food delivery

PATHAO LTD. AND SHOHOZ.

2020

when the covid 19 came ride sharing was totally off. then i started delivering food with pathao and shohoz Itd.

## Freelancing

FREELANCER.COM

2020 - 2021

After Learning Photoshop and illustrator, I started freelancing.I made lots of brand identity and joined lots of contest here.

## **PRIVATE COURSES**

## Computer World

Master Of Graphic Design

Six months course covered adobe photoshop, illustrator, premiere pro, ms excel, ms word, how to freelance and more.

## **Ueropean It Institute**

Modern Javascript Es6

3 month course covered html, css, javascript es6. i have completed this course and got certified. after that i have learned so many things on youtube related javascript.

## Udemy.com

Webdriver IO And Linux

2022

online course covered webdriver io with appium 2.0. and linux, i have done total three courses in udemy and got certified. after that i have learned postman from youtube.

## **Programming Hero**

Complete Web Devolopment

2022

online course covered a to z of web devolopment with reactjs, nodejs, expressjs, mongodb, sass, bootstrap, tailwind css. i have completed this course and got certified.

# **HARD-SKILLS**

## **DEVOLOPMENT**

CSS

SASS

TAILWIND CSS

**JAVASCRIPT** 

MONGODB

EXPRESS JS

REACT JS

NODE JS

FIREBASE

#### **AUTOMATION**

WEBDRIVER IO

APPIUM 2.0

**POSTMAN** 

**JENKINS** 

## **DESIGN**

IN-DESIGN

**ILLUSTRATOR** 

PHOTOSHOP

PREMIER PRO

#### OFFICE

MS EXCEL

MS WORD

**OPERATING** 

WINDOWS

GNU LINUX

#### COMUPTER

TYPING SP. 80+ WPM

WER BROWSING

RESEARCHING

TROUBLESHOOTING

# **SOFT-SKILLS**

#### LISTENING

ASKING QUESTIONS

**PUNCTUALITY** 

## COMMUNICATION

ACTIVE LISTENING

HANDLING CRTICISM

**PATIENCE** 

#### **CUSTOMER SERVICE**

**EMPATHY** 

**NEGOTIATION** 

PROBLEM SOLVING

## **LANGUAGES**

**ENGLISH** 

BANGLA

HINDI

## **LEADERSHIP**

PLANNING

CRITICAL THINKING

TRUSTWORTHINESS

DECISION-MAKING

ABILITY TO TEACH

# MANAGEMENT

FLEXIBILITY

ADAPTIBILITY

RESPONSIBILITY TIME MANAGEMENT

EXP. PAPERWORKS

## **INTEREST**

**PYTHON** 

DATA SCIENCE

All of my education, courses, and experiences listed here I did from Dhaka, Bangladesh where I was born on 06 March 1999. I will join your company with all of my learnings and will try to do my best to boost your daily work flow up. I enjoy taking on responsibilities because that's how I can actually challenge myself and know my true potential. Thank you.